{
    "subject": "Max_Jacoby",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Dust__2009_film_",
    "human_readable": "Max Jacoby created the film Dust (2009).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.77457195520401,
            "question": "Who created the film Dust?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7642791271209717,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by Max Jacoby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5951698422431946,
            "question": "What year was the film Dust released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5358285307884216,
            "question": "Is Dust a recent movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.482357382774353,
            "question": "Was Dust a successful film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46085551381111145,
            "question": "Do you know any other films made by Max Jacoby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3346613645553589,
            "question": "What genre might the film Dust belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33314236998558044,
            "question": "Where could I find more information about the film Dust?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23937492072582245,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of Dust?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18512485921382904,
            "question": "What awards or recognition did Dust receive?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Max Jacoby created the film Dust (2009).",
            "html": "yago_12235_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the plot of Dust?",
            "html": "yago_12235_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where could I find more information about the film Dust?",
            "html": "yago_12235_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre might the film Dust belong to?",
            "html": "yago_12235_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12235_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12235_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12235_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12235_133.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12235_149.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12235_165.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12235_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12235_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12235_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12235_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{'output': 'no'}\n\nThe reason is that there are two different films named \"Dust\" mentioned in the documents. One of them is a feature film directed by Max Jacoby and produced in Luxembourg (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_12235/re-ranker-msmarco/95.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_12235/re-ranker-msmarco/13.txt), and the other one is an American video production company that produces sci-fi short films (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_12235/re-ranker-msmarco/109.txt). The latter does not seem to be related to Max Jacoby, so it's unlikely that he created the film \"Dust\" mentioned in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_12235/re-ranker-msmarco/109.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The documents mention that Max Jacoby is a Luxembourgian film director who graduated in 2001 from the London International Film School. They also provide information about his first feature film, DUST, which was made in 2009. This supports the triple that Max Jacoby created the film \"Dust\" (2009)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}